it has been a long two weeks i've been
in the process of moving and it's been
daunting at times
i'm slowly settling in and unpacking my
things
i'm certainly not moved in yet and the
process is taking longer than i
anticipated
i am currently moving into the second
story of the house since luke and his
father have not yet finished the
downstairs
as you may already know this home used
to be an open stable for horses but i've
decided to call this top story the tree
house because it definitely feels like
one
everything from the wood walls to the
elevated view of the pine trees out of
every window makes me feel like i'm in a
little forest home nestled between the
tree branches and the sky
[Music]
i like the smaller rooms and simple
nostalgic feel of the wood walls
it doesn't feel like home yet but i know
it will in time
making a space cozy is very important to
me it may sound rather strange but i
personally have found that if i unpack
and decorate in a frenzied and anxious
state of mind it feels as if i imbue
that feeling into the new space
making the process of settling in more
difficult
by taking deep breaths and trying to
keep my heart calm during big changes
taking as much time as i can
i find it makes the transition much more
gentle and healthy
i will show you a walkthrough of the
space at the end of this video and i
would love any decorating tips or ideas
you have
i also appreciate your patience during
this time of transition since i can't
make my more usual type of videos
i do have this old desk which my father
gifted to me when i was a teenager
plus several other antique or secondhand
items that i've been able to take out of
my parents home where they have been
stored
i love earthy colors and definitely want
to bring more life into this space
moving forward in these videos you will
be seeing a lot more trees as we are in
the forest now
also my future in-laws have a really
lovely dog and cat who i'm sure will be
introducing themselves soon enough
[Music]
do
so
[Music]
do
so i did want to give you a bit of a
walk through so i appreciate your
patience with my camera
this space feels so different from what
i'm used to i'm definitely excited to
have an actual stove and running water
all year round which is a huge bonus
when i first walked in here i felt like
it was the set of an old tv show maybe
made in the 90s the style of the
apartment definitely feels like it's
from a slightly different time and i
really like it
perhaps the thing i'm most excited about
in regards to this new space is that i
have an actual bathroom as you know
in my last home it was just a simple
compost toilet and it is nice to have a
working shower
as you can see this place is ready to be
lived in luke's parents used to rent
this top story out with a kitchenette
and bathroom and so it is all ready for
someone to live up here if needed which
is useful since the bottom level of the
house isn't complete
but i'm not living here full time right
now because i'm still in the process of
moving i'm kind of dividing my time
between my parents home and here
so this back room could either be a
bedroom or perhaps a little working
space for art and craft projects we are
not sure yet but i do know that i think
these walls are very lovely they're an
old cedar and put here a long time ago
i also think we'll have to take out the
carpet at some point it's fairly old and
perhaps a new layer or at least a carpet
to cover it would freshen up the space
and i suppose that is the tour i do
really like it i think spaces like this
can definitely feel very different after
you've moved in with a bit of decorating
so far i've sourced the majority of what
i have from thrift stores and secondhand
shops i'm excited to see how this place
forms and how i feel about it in a few
months i did go to a craft store
recently and picked up some knobs and
other little metal handles that i think
will personalize the space quite a bit
and they were only a couple dollars so
i'm gonna get creative and give you an
update as i go
so i hope you can hear me my audio setup
is not super great right now
but yeah i wanted to just um
check in and say hello because
it's been a little while since i
uploaded i knew i
at least had to have a week off to be
able to
prepare
moving and all that and
what taking a week off has taught me has
been that moving is a lot more involved
and takes a lot more time than just one
week
so i'm definitely learning a lot and
taking it one step at a time and taking
a lot of deep breaths
it's really interesting to
walk through a home that isn't yours
after you have created such a strong
connection with the one you already had
and so i'm looking forward to creating a
closer relationship
with this space and
feeling more cozy and at home here very
soon i am however so excited to
start this new chapter and
you know have fun decorating i already
found a couple items at my local thrift
store for a few dollars that i think
will be really wonderful i have a old
desk an antique desk that was gifted to
me by my father years ago that he also
found at a thrift store an antique shop
and
i am very excited to
use it here since i've never had room
for it at my old
house
so
i don't have anywhere to do my art or
bake or work on a lot of things right
now besides an office space
and i
feel a little bit in limbo of course
which is natural
but it is very difficult to create a
video but i do hope that by next week i
will be able to have settled in a lot
more and have a lot more to show you
and i actually would really love to make
some videos about decorating and how i
decorate on a very minimal budget but
also how i'm going to be preparing my
garden because i'm actually going to
have room for a proper garden over here
um but yes i would love to share all
that with you
and
yeah this all feels really weird i have
to admit i think it's just so many
transitions you know and
ah yeah but
it's gonna be okay you're taking it a
day at a time and change can be really
uncomfortable sometimes but that doesn't
mean it's not worth it
now tell me if i'm crazy but i do feel
like
certain
houses have different kind of feelings
associated with them bear with me i
don't want to sound like super silly but
my cottage felt very peaceful and very
serene because
while i was there i really worked on
having it be a space that no matter how
stressful long 14-hour day at work it
was i would come home and then my
cottage was the space to rest and a
space to
you know enjoy
my hobbies and interests and
here i do feel very a very similar
feeling of it feeling very peaceful but
right now it feels peaceful but just so
empty so
void of kind of life and
memories and all that so i definitely
need to
create that story in this house and it
seems like such a sweet house anyway
thank you again i really really
appreciate all your support of my etsy
shop during this time it has meant a lot
it has been something i've been able to
hold on to during this time and really
focus on and it has really helped me
stay a lot more calm and relaxed during
this time because i've had a very
specific set of projects i need to get
done and people to communicate with so
so thank you for that and thank you for
all the encouraging messages you have
sent
with your orders so i really appreciate
that well i think i'm gonna try to go
get busy and make this house a home at
least a little bit more of a home
until you guys see me again
and yes i will see you very soon let me
know if you have any questions about the
house and i will try to answer them in a
future video
so i'm wishing you all the very best
goodbye
[Music]
you